[
 {
    "quizName":"HTML Quiz",
    "quizId":1,
    "questions":[
        {
            "question":"What is HTML?",
            "options":[
                "HTML describes the structure of a webpage",
                "HTML is the standard markup language mainly used to create web pages",
                "HTML consists of a set of elements that helps the browser how to view the content",
                "All of the mentioned"
            ],
            "answer":4,
            "id":11
        },
        {
            "question":"Who is the father of HTML?",
            "options":[
                "Rasmus Lerdorf",
                "Tim Berners-Lee",
                "Brendan Eich",
                "Sergey Brin"
            ],
            "id":12,
            "answer":2
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the correct syntax of doctype in HTML5?",
            "options":[
                "</doctype html>",
                " <doctype html>",
                " <doctype html!>",
                "<!doctype html>"
            ],
            "answer":4,
            "id":13
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following is used to read an HTML page and render it?",
            "options":[
                "Web server",
                "Web network",
                "Web browser",
                "Web matrix"
            ],
            "answer":3,
            "id":14
        }
    ]
 },
 {
    "quizName":"CSS Quiz",
    "quizId":2,
    "questions":[
        {
            "question":"What is CSS?",
            "options":[
                "CSS is a style sheet language",
                "CSS is designed to separate the presentation and content, including layout, colors, and fonts",
                "CSS is the language used to style the HTML documents",
                "All of the mentioned"
            ],
            "answer":4,
            "id":11
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following tag is used to embed css in html page?",
            "options":[
                "<css>",
                "<!DOCTYPE html>",
                "<script>",
                "<style>"
            ],
            "id":12,
            "answer":4
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following CSS selectors are used to specify a group of elements?",
            "options":[
                "tag",
                "id",
                "class",
                "both class and tag"
            ],
            "answer":3,
            "id":13
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following has introduced text, list, box, margin, border, color, and background properties?",
            "options":[
                "HTML",
                "PHP",
                "CSS",
                "Ajax"
            ],
            "answer":3,
            "id":14
        }
    ]
 },
 {
    "quizName":"Science Quiz",
    "quizId":3,
    "questions":[
        {
            "question":"What is the PH of H2O?",
            "options":[
                "6",
                "7",
                "8",
                "9"
            ],
            "answer":2,
            "id":11
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following gas is reduced in the reduction process?",
            "options":[
                "Oxygen",
                "Helium",
                "Carbon",
                "Hydrogen"
            ],
            "id":12,
            "answer":4
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following compound is mainly used in hand sanitizer?",
            "options":[
                "Aldehyde",
                "Acetic acid",
                "Alcohol",
                "Ketone"
            ],
            "answer":3,
            "id":13
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the S.I unit of frequency?",
            "options":[
                "Diopter",
                "Second",
                "Hertz",
                "Meter"
            ],
            "answer":3,
            "id":14
        },
        {
            "question":"Acid turns blue litmus paper into which color?",
            "options":[
                "Black",
                "Blue",
                "Red",
                "Orange"
            ],
            "answer":3,
            "id":15
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following enzymes is not present in the human stomach?",
            "options":[
                "Pepsin",
                "Hydrochloric acid",
                "Mucus",
                "Trypsin"
            ],
            "answer":4,
            "id":16
        },
        {
            "question":"Which of the following gland is present in the human mouth?",
            "options":[
                "Adrenal",
                "Pituitary",
                "Gonads",
                "Salivary"
            ],
            "answer":4,
            "id":17
        },
        {
            "question":"Name the gland which is present above our kidneys?",
            "options":[
                "Adrenal",
                "Pituitary",
                "Gonads",
                "Salivary"
            ],
            "answer":1,
            "id":18
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the basic unit of our neural system?",
            "options":[
                "Neutron",
                "Neuron",
                "Nephron",
                "Nucleon"
            ],
            "answer":2,
            "id":19
        },
        {
            "question":"What is the basic unit of our excretory system?",
            "options":[
                "Neutron",
                "Neuron",
                "Nephron",
                "Nucleon"
            ],
            "answer":3,
            "id":20
        }
    ]
 }
]